Data Privacy Policy of DOG Productions Ltd.

Dorado Games respects your right to control your privacy. We have put in place security measures for your personal data and manage your personal data in accordance with applicable data protection and data privacy regulations. This Privacy Policy explains how we handle and treat your data when you (i) register or visit our site, \[www.conflictnations.com\] or associated sites or pages (the ”Website”), (ii) use our services, or (iii) engage or communicate with us. It also provides information about your rights relating to your Personal Data.

Throughout this Privacy Policy the following terms have the following meanings:

**”Data Privacy Laws”** means applicable data protection and data privacy laws and regulations, including but not limited to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (2016/679) (the ”**GDPR**”).

“**Processing**” and “**Process**” means all activities involving your Personal Data, including collecting, handling, storing, sharing, accessing, using, transferring and disposing of information.

"**Services**" means our applications and other products, the Website, email communications, social media accounts and any related services or properties we control.

"**Personal Data**" means Personal Data that relates to you as an identified or identifiable individual.

All capitalised terms not specifically defined herein shall have the meaning ascribed to such terms in the GDPR.

While operating the Services, Personal Data will be shared with partners we work with. Some of these partners are Controllers independently of us and, therefore, independently determine how and why they process your data. For more information on these partners and the ways in which they may process your data, please refer to section 4 of this Privacy Policy. Under certain circumstances we will transfer your Personal Data to countries outside the European Economic Area. Such transfers will be done in accordance with section 5 of this Privacy Policy.

Our Services are not directed to children and we do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under 16 years of age.

**1\. Who are we**

_Controller_

The Controller responsible for your Personal Data for the purposes of the GDPR is:

DOG Productions Ltd

The Hedge Business Centre, Triq ir-Rampa, St Julians, STJ1217

E-Mail: [\[email protected\]](https://www.conflictnations.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Website: [www.doradogames.com](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.doradogames.com/&sa=D&ust=1606749797299000&usg=AOvVaw15FlMOhQ_nfjKMUDAzle4e)

hereinafter referred to as the "**Company**", "**we**", "**us**", or "**our**".

The principles set out in this Privacy Policy apply to all instances in which the Company Processes your personal data as a Controller for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. The Company is part of the Stillfront Group, a global group of gaming studios with its parent company, Stillfront Group AB (publ), incorporated in Sweden and listed on Nasdaq Stockholm.

_Data Protection Officer_

The data protection officer of the Controller for the purposes of the GDPR is:

Peter Birgersson, Deloitte AB

Contact details: [\[email protected\]](https://www.conflictnations.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**2\. What information do we collect from you?**

Information you provide voluntarily when using our services such as playing our games:

Your name, email address, or other contact information communicated to us.

Any Personal Data provided in any communication channel available in our Services.

Account information such as nickname, email and chosen login method.

If you have subscribed to our communications, your content preferences or other information you submit to us when subscribing to our communications.

If you participate in our surveys or other research, any comments, feedback, resoonses, or other information you provide to us when doing so.

Any other information you choose to submit to us through our Services or otherwise.

Directly from you and/or your device by automatic means:

Your device and browser: Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device, such as your device type, model, manufacturer, operating system, language, display, processor, the Internet browser type you are using, and your IP address (including your coarse location).

Your use of our Services: We track and collect usage data, such as the date and time you access our Services, access status, duration of use of our Services, the site you visited, the information and files that have been downloaded.

Crash logs or other information related to bugs, errors, or other issues in our Services.

Inferences we make based on your activity in our Services.

_The Company collects Personal Data directly from you and/or your device (such as your phone or computer) by automatic means when you use our Services or interact with your ads outside of our Services on third-party websites or applications, including through cookies or similar technologies or software development kits (SDKs). For more information regarding the Company's ue of cookies, please view our Cookie Policy._

We do not expect or intend to collect or otherwise process any special categories of data relating to you. By special categories of data, we mean genetic, biometric or health information, information revealing racial or ethnic origin, sex life or sexual orientation, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, or information about your criminal offences or convictions. Please do not provide this kind of information to us or use the Services to make it available to others.

3\. How do we use your Personal Data

We use your Personal Data for different purposes. We will for example use the Personal Data to provide you with the Services you have requested, to improve and develop our Services, to predict user trends, to make recommendations and marketing activities based on your usage and to customise our Services to you, these include the following processing activities:

Processing is necessary to perform our contract with you in respect of our Services:

Information provided voluntarily by you is used to enable you to use our Services and administer the Services.

Information provided voluntarily by you and automatically collected data is used to provide, maintain, enhance and personalise the Service(s) (including selecting an appropriate language version for you based on your location).

To take the appropriate actions in accordance with our Terms and Conditions and Game rules.

Automatically collected data is used to know your preferences and to try to ensure that the content on our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer or mobile device, based on your browsing history on our services.

Information provided voluntarily by you is used to send you newsletters or other similar communications if you have subscribed to them (for example, through a subscription form on our Websites).

Based on our legitimate interest to make our Services the best they can be and provide you with the best possible user experience in our Services

Information provided voluntarily by you and automatically collected data is used to operate and maintain our Services (improve our current Services or develop new Services) including troubleshoot or debug any bugs, errors, or other issues in our Services.

Information provided voluntarily by you and automatically collected data is used to, where available, provide social features (such as chat and forum functions) or events in our Services or other Services.

Contact information provided by you is used for the purpose of contacting you and/or handling your support requests or otherwise managing our relationship with you.

Automatically collected data is used to measure and analyse the use of our Services or data we collect through our Services (for example, to discover trends or other insights or to inform our operations).

Data provided by you as well as automatically collected data is used to create data that is not identifiable to you (for example, aggregate data), which we then use and share freely.

Automatically collected data is used to analyse how visitors use our Services.

Based on our legitimate interest to make our services more intuitive and evaluate user behaviours and preferences.

Automatically generated data, that is not identifiable to you, specifically aggregated data regarding recency and frequency of player events such as “game closed” or “in-app purchases” is analysed to understand retention patterns and player behaviour.

Based on our legitimate interest to market our services.

Account information such as email address is used to market our and our affiliate services that we believe might interest you.

Account information is used to conduct marketing campaigns for our and affiliated services.

Information collected and submitted to us is used to operate, optimise and measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

Based on our legitimate interest to facilitate performance marketing.

Automatically generated data, that is not identifiable to you, specifically aggregated data regarding recency and frequency of player events such as “watched in-game advertising” or “in-app purchases” is used to understand and measure player lifetime value. Through this data, we can analyse expected future revenue from our players.

Based on our legitimate interest to provide you with interest-based services and contextual advertisement.

We use ad identifiers, third-party tracking ID's (such as AppsFlyer ID) and similar technologies to collect data from your device. Information from third party providers is combined with features including device type, system language and IP address to create a unique player ID. This is done for the purpose of recognising you and your device and providing you with customised player experiences and interest-based advertising.

Based on our legitimate interest to safguard our operations.

Information provided voluntarily by you and automatically collected data is used to audit our operations or processes (for example, to verify that they function as intended).

Processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the controller is subject.

For example in the unlikely event of a dispute or a criminal investigation. Where required by law, your Personal Data will be disclosed to an applicable governmental, regulatory, sporting or enforcement authority. Your Personal Data will also be disclosed to any regulatory body in connection with prevention and detection of crime and where the Company considers that there are reasonable grounds to suspect that you may be involved in a breach of the law. Those bodies will then use your Personal Data to investigate and act on any such breaches in accordance with their procedures.

In addition, we may process your data for additional purposes which are compatiable with any of the purposes listed above.

4\. Who we share your information with

Your Personal Data will (for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy) be transferred or disclosed to third parties, for the processing of that Personal Data on our behalf, such as to:

* Other companies in the Stillfront Group, where they help us develop, administrate, market or operate our and affiliated Services will receive access to all available and required Personal Data. For information on the entities within Stillfront Group, see the most recent annual report published on https://www.stillfront.com/en/reports-presentations/, as updated from time to time.
* For analytical, and optimization purposes, we collect and transfer automatically generated data such as your recent visits to our services and how you move around different sections, in order to make our services more intuitive and evaluate user needs and preferences. This data will be shared with a limited group of employees in the Stillfront Group.
* Persons or companies that provide services to us and process Personal Data on our behalf when providing those services.
* Professional advisors such as external legal and audit services etc. Personal Data shared will consist of information you provide voluntarily when using our Services and data collected from your device by automatic means.
* Third parties to whom we outsource or collaborate with for certain services such as, without limitation, document processing and translation services, marketing, confidential waste disposal, IT systems or software providers, IT Support service providers, document and information storage providers such as Dropbox, Amazon Web Services, etc. Data shared will consist of information you provide voluntarily when using our Services and data collected from your device by automatic means.
* Third party services when you link, connect or login on our services with a third party service. The third party service will then share your necessary information such as email for the specific purpose with us or as otherwise authorised by your settings.
* Competent courts of law or other government authorities where we believe disclosure is necessary as a matter of applicable law or regulation, such as the Authority for Privacy Protection in relation to any scrutiny of compliance with GDPR.
* Any person or entity where we believe disclosure is necessary to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights or to protect your or another person's vital interests.
* Please note this list is non-exhaustive and there may be other examples where we need to share data with other parties in order to provide the Services as effectively as we can

When Personal Data is shared with our business partners, group affiliates or other trusted entities stated above, we always require them to only use information in accordance with our instructions.

5\. Appropriate Safeguards to countries outside the EU/EEA-area

In connection with some processing activities described in this Privacy Policy we share information outside of the European Union (“**EU**”) and the European Economic Area (“**EEA**”). For example, a number of servers and service providers we use for hosting and processing data are located in the United States, and some of our group companies we collaborate with to provide and optimise the Services may be located outside of the EU and the EEA. Where the Company transfers Personal Data outside the EU/EEA, The Company will ensure that Standard Contractual Clauses have been entered into between the transferring entity and the receiving external party. Additional safeguards will also be put in place prior to such transfers.

Data shared will consist of information you provide voluntarily when using our Services and data collected from your device by automatic means. You are under Data Privacy Laws upon request entitled to receive a copy of any documentation demonstrating that appropriate safeguards have been taken in order to protect your Personal Data during a transfer outside the EU/EEA. You can do so by reaching out to our Data Processing Officer [\[email protected\]](https://www.conflictnations.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

6\. How long do we keep hold of your information?

We will retain your information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We are using the following criteria to establish our retention period: (i) as long as we have an ongoing relationship with you; (ii) as required by legal obligations to which the Company is subject (such as tax and accounting obligations); and (iii) as advisable in light of our legal position (such as applicable statutes of limitations). For more specific information about data retention terms, please contact our Data Processing Officer [\[email protected\]](https://www.conflictnations.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will provide the specific data retention terms for your jurisdiction.

7\. Security

Your data is secured by appropriate safeguards, taking into account the circumstances, the state of the art, the costs of implementation and the nature, scope, context and purposes of processing as well as the risk. In support of this commitment, we have implemented appropriate technical, physical and organisational measures to protect your Personal Data against unauthorised or accidental destruction, alteration or disclosure; misuse; damage; theft or accidental loss; or unauthorised access.

We process the data collected from you in accordance with Maltese and European data protection law.

All employees are required to protect data privacy and comply with data protection regulation, and are trained accordingly.

For payment purposes, your data is transmitted using the SSL process and encrypted.

8\. Your Rights

Providing data to us is not mandatory. However, we are unable to provide the Services, or some parts or features of the Services, without processing your data. If you use our Services, we will collect data relating to you for some or all the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, depending on the Services you decide to use and your choices when using them. You have a number of options to limit or control the extent to which your data is processed. For example, you can choose to not connect your third-party accounts with our Services, use your device settings to reset or limit the use of your Advertising ID, or disable some or all cookies from your browser settings.

In relation to our processing of your Personal Data you have, under certain circumstances, the right to exercise the following rights:

* _Access_
* You may request confirmation whether or not Personal Data is processed and, if that is the case, access to your Personal Data and additional information such as the purposes of the processing. You are also entitled to receive a copy of the Personal Data undergoing processing. If the request is made by electronic means the information will be provided in a commonly used electronic format if you do not request otherwise.
* _Object to certain processing_
* You may object to the processing of your Personal Data on the basis of a legitimate interest, on grounds relating to your particular situation and to the processing for direct marketing purposes. To unsubscribe from our marketing communications, please use the unsubscribe link provided in the messages we send. The unsubscribe link is typically found at the end of the message.
* _Rectification_
* You have at any time the right to have inaccurate Personal Data rectified, as well as, taking into account the purposes of the processing, the right to have incomplete Personal Data completed.
* _Erasure_
* You may have your Personal Data erased under certain circumstances such as when your Personal Data is no longer needed for the purposes for which it was collected.
* _Restriction of processing_
* You may ask us to restrict the processing of your Personal Data to only comprise storage of your Personal Data under certain circumstances, such as when the processing is unlawful, but you do not wish your Personal Data erased.
* _Withdrawal of Consent_
* You have the right to at any time withdraw your consent to processing of Personal Data to the extent the processing is based on your consent. This does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.
* _Data Portability_
* You may ask to receive a machine-readable copy of Personal Data processed and ask for the information to be transferred to another Controller (where possible). This only refers to such Personal Data processed on the basis of your consent or on the basis that the processing is necessary in order to perform an agreement with you and only to the extent the Personal Data has been provided to the Company by you (data portability).
* _Complaints to the supervisory authority_
* You have the right to lodge complaints pertaining to the processing of your Personal Data to the relevant data protection supervisory authority.
* _How to adjust your preferences_
* If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our data collection practices, please contact us at the address or email set out under section 1 of this Privacy Policy and specify your country of residence and the nature of your question.

9\. Changes to the terms of this Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, for example due to changes in our operations or the legal obligations that apply to us. Updates will be made available here. We will also inform you of any changes by other means that are appropriate to the significance of the changes.

Last updated: 2024-08-13

US RESIDENTS

If you are based in the United States and connecting from states in which data protection laws have been enacted this section forms part of the Privacy Policy and should be read together with the other sections of the Privacy Policy. If there is any conflict between this section and the remainder of the Privacy Policy, this section shall prevail.Dorado Games\] does not sell personal data and has not done so in the last 12 months. We may share identifiers and cookie information with our third-party advertisement platforms to provide you with interest based and personalized advertisements, attribute installs and optimize our marketing, to the extent such practices are considered a “sale” under Applicable Data Protection Law you may opt out by following the steps below. For more information on our personal data collection please see the sections in this Privacy Policy concerning our data processing.

* _Opt Out_
* You have the right to opt-out of the sale or sharing of your personal information by us for targeted advertising purposes, “sale” or for profiling with Legal or significant effect on you. How to opt out is dependent on the service you use, for more information see section 8 of this privacy policy. Your opt out may be limited to the specific service.
* _Access and Data Portability:_
* You may have the right to request details about the Personal Data we have collected about you. You may also have the right to receive a copy of your Personal Data.
* _Right to Correction_
* You may have the right to request we correct incorrect or inaccurate Personal Data, subject to restrictions regarding the determination of accuracy of the existing Personal Data.
* _Right to Deletion_
* You may have the right to request deletion of your Personal data unless an exception applies.
* _Right to nondiscrimination_
* We will not change the quality of our services, deny you access or provide a different level of quality if you choose to exercise these rights, unless allowed or required under applicable law. Some rights might impact the usage and availability of certain services, such as personalization and deletion.
* _Right to Appeal_
* If we deny or reject your privacy rights request, you may have a right to appeal our decision if permitted by your state’s privacy law.
* _Right of limitation;_
* Depending on your state of residence you may have the right to ask us to limit the use of your sensitive personal information if we use it to infer characteristics about you. To exercise this right please use the provided opt out tools or contact us under the method described in section 8. Your right to limitation is subject to exception and depending on the state we will obtain your consent before collection of sensitive personal information.

California Shine the Light (only applicable on California residents)

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information (as defined by applicable California law) in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the prior calendar year. To obtain this information please send an email message to [\[email protected\]](https://www.conflictnations.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with “Request for California Privacy Information” on the subject line and in the body of your message. We may require you to verify your identity, and the information is limited to that covered by the California Shine the light law under this request.
